JOSÉ MARÍA GONZÁLEZ CRUZ

FRONT-END DEVELOPER JR.



5610808771



josmara301@hotmail.com



https://portfoliojose.netlify.app



www.linkedin.com/in/gonzálezcruzjosémaría

ABOUT

I am a passionate Junior Frontend Developer with a specialized focus on React Native and Js. My career is characterized by the perfect combination of technical skills and soft skills that make me a valuable asset in any development team as well as developing APIs with Spring Boot, I am ready to contribute to the success of challenging projects and continue growing as a professional in the exciting world of software development.

LOGIEET

EDUCATION

APPLIED MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTING

FES ACATLAN - UNAM AUGUST 2019 – JUNE 2023

SKILLS

- Development and layout of web interfaces.
- Object-Oriented Programming.
- Methodologies for system development.
- Documented and clean program.

LENGUAGES

- English (intermediate b1)
- Spanish (native)

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- React Native (1 year).
- React Js. (2 years)
- JavaScript (2 years)
- Python (1 year)
- Java (1 year)
- TypeScript (1 year)
- Node Js. (2years)
- MySQL (6 months)

EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023

FRONT-END DEVELOPER JR.

Participate in the creation of an e-commerce system that breaks down payments and income into Telcel recharge purchases. The following technologies were used:

- · React Js.
- · REDUX storage info from the API.
- · SASS for styling.
- · Consumption of APIS (AXIOS)
- Using as frameworks:
 - React chart to show charts about payments made by user and telcel stores.
 - CHAKRA UI its a component library.
- · SCRUM methodologies.

2021 -Actually

MASKSOFT

FULL STACK DEVELOPER JR.

Participate in the creation of a dental system, for sales, quotes, pdfs, finances, APIS creation and information breakdown.

The following technologies were used:

- · React Js.
- Spring Boot to create APIS.
- REDUX storage info from the API.
- · SASS for styling.
- · Consumption of APIS (AXIOS).
- Google APIS integration to login, register and get events from Google Calendar.
- · Using as frameworks:
 - Bootstrap 5 ist's a component library.
 - Use of PAYPAL and Mercado Pago for pay licence of the system.
- SCRUM methodologies.

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- · Emotional intelligence
- · Time management
- Responsible
- Initiative
- Communication skills